
[
        {
            "Topic": "General Knowledge",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Demolition",
            "options": [
                "The Dream Team",
                "The Bushwhackers",
                "The British Bulldogs",
                "Demolition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "History",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "6",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "3",
                "7",
                "6"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Books",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Astoria Greengrass",
            "options": [
                "Pansy Parkinson",
                "Millicent Bulstrode",
                "Hermione Granger",
                "Astoria Greengrass"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Science: Computers",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "2000",
            "options": [
                "1998",
                "1999",
                "2001",
                "2000"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Ocarina of Time",
            "options": [
                "Majora&#039;s Mask",
                "A Link to the Past",
                "The Wind Waker",
                "Ocarina of Time"
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Mario Tennis",
            "options": [
                "Mario Party 3",
                "Mario Kart: Double Dash!!",
                "Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour",
                "Mario Tennis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Casserole",
            "options": [
                "Sub Sandwich",
                "Chicken Soup",
                "Pepperoni Pizza",
                "Casserole"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Carmen",
            "options": [
                "Don Rodrigue",
                "Gris&eacute;lidis",
                "Les p&ecirc;cheurs de perles",
                "Carmen"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Music",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Illmatic",
            "options": [
                "The Low End Theory",
                "The Chronic",
                "Enter The Wu-Tang (36 Chambers)",
                "Illmatic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "20,000",
            "options": [
                "128",
                "10,000",
                "5,000",
                "20,000"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Arbok",
            "options": [
                "Linoone",
                "Tauros",
                "Nidoking",
                "Arbok"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Music",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Pink Floyd",
            "options": [
                "AC/DC",
                "Metallica",
                "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
                "Pink Floyd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Solid Snake",
            "options": [
                "Pit",
                "Meta Knight",
                "R.O.B.",
                "Solid Snake"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "9",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "6",
                "10",
                "9"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Shiron",
            "options": [
                "Jack",
                "Axia",
                "Drum",
                "Shiron"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Celebrities",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Moose",
            "options": [
                "Dog",
                "Bear",
                "Goat",
                "Moose"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "Blinkmoth Infusion",
            "options": [
                "Vitalizing Wind",
                " Chant of Vitu-Ghazi",
                "Assert Authority",
                "Blinkmoth Infusion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Topic": "General Knowledge",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "",
            "correct_answer": "The inability to stand up",
            "options": [
                "The inability to make decisions",
                "The inability to concentrate on anything",
                "A feverish desire to rip one&#039;s clothes off",
                "The inability to stand up"
            ]
        }
    ]
